(Sheldon:)No, I went to punch
the water fountain,
(Sheldon:)slipped in water in front
of the water fountain,
(Sheldon:)and hit my head
on the water fountain.
(Bernadette:)I can't imagine you
being violent.
(Leonard:)It's not hard.
Just picture the Three Stooges,
(Leonard:)and then take away two stooges.
(Sheldon:)I'm so disappointed
in myself.
(Sheldon:)Jealousy is
completely illogical.
(Raj:)It's a human
emotion, Sheldon.
(Raj:)Everyone gets jealous.
(Raj:)I'm jealous of
Leonard and Penny
(Raj:)and Howard and Bernadette
(Raj:)for being in such
happy relationships.
(Amy:)What about me and Sheldon?
(Bernadette:)Sure.
(Leonard:)I've always been jealous
of how much money
(Leonard:)Raj's family has.
(Raj:)Thank you for saying that.
Next to buying things,
(Raj:)that is the best part
about having money.
(Amy:)Ever since I met Penny,
(Amy:)I've been envious
of her looks.
(Penny:)Aw, thank you.
(Amy:)That's why I was so happy
when you cut your hair off.
What?!
(Amy:)You know what I mean.